Green laver expedition!
Green laver explorer!
Ah!
Midiro!
Green laver Munsterlust!
The last of the sea nori exploration!
Please take care of them!
So, these two are here today, right?
Yes!
Today's exploration
We'll be using only recorded audio.
on location!
Wow!
What's that? There's a bird, there's a bird.
Let's film on location using only recorded audio.
We usually explore the eBinz building as usual, but we are getting used to it,
Today, we are going to do a mission, or rather, a project,
The voice memo on your phone... Don't look like Shinichi Mori.
Are you Shinichi Mori?
I'm not asking you to clap.
There is a function on your smartphone called "voice memo," right?
I asked the two of you to record words that you could use on location in advance,
Then, they would go on location using only those words.
No talking is allowed.
The place we were going to was e-earphones.
Wow!
LoL
Recommendations and stuff like that.
That kind of thing to the clerk.
Go ask a lot of questions.
Okay, let's move on to the store.
Let's go to the store.
Let's go!
We've arrived at the E-earphone store.
From here, right?
Please use only your cell phone's voice memo
alone.
Thank you very much.
I'm Ritsuki Hikaru.
I'm Ritsuki Itaru.
Pleased to meet you.
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
What are you doing?
We're Ritsuki Hikaru to each other.
Let's go next.
What's going on?
Don't go on your own.
We've got a lot of audio on our phones.
Use it.
Ask the clerks for recommendations.
Is that okay?
Okay.
You're very excited.
Well, can I call the waiter now?
Can you two take over from here?
I'll call him.
Yes, please.
Hello.
I'm Cassy from Earphones Sendai Ekimae.
Nice to meet you.
It's getting exciting!
Really?
Shall we go?
I'm looking forward to it.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Ritsuki Hikaru.
The second one.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Well then, let me introduce you.
I hope you all know who I am.
Mr. Talk's corner!
Yes, yes.
Do you know it?
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Actually, Yu Fujitani tuned the sound for this.
Cream soda.
I know.
You don't remember?
Huh?
It's a cream soda.
That's awesome.
I'd like to recommend this one first.
Wow!
These earphones were originally made for the Sendai Earphone Sendai Ekimae Store's collaboration with Ikinari Talk's earphone general election event.
The members were divided into three teams to make the earphones, and Mr. Fujitani was on Team Cream Solar and Ms. Hikaru Ritsugi was on Team Ritsugi Solar.
And Hikaru Ritsugi made the earphones for a team called Team Pyon.
Unfortunately, Pyon was not selected, but Ms. Fujitani's "Cream Solar" won the 200 millionth prize and the earphones were made into a product.
Can you see them?
This Cream Soda is now on sale and we hope you will give it a try.
This one is priced at 19,800 yen.
Is it cheap?
Please open your mouth.
Now, let's move on to the wireless headphone corner.
Here they are!
If there are any wireless headphones you are interested in, let's try them on, like hanging them around your neck.
Do you have any recommendations?
How about something cute like Marshall's?
It's so loud!
It's like you're wearing it wrong.
I'm just saying it's cute.
What do you think? What do you think of it?
No, you didn't.
The sound quality is great!
Is it better than it sounds? It really is.
I'll take everything from here to here.
Thank you very much.
Let's do the math.
Open your mouth, please.
Next, we have a wireless earphone corner.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to introduce the cheapest wireless earphones.
Right this way.
The price is 1480 yen!
But it's expensive, isn't it?
I said it's the cheapest.
End of summer
Do you have earphones that go with this?
These?
They'll fit me.
I'm a Japanese girl.
This pink one is cute. I'm a girl.
It's cute.
That's my first impression.
Okay, now, I've done the audio and I've done the location shooting.
I'd like to explain again what you just saw without the sound.
First of all, this is what we did, right?
I did it with Cream Soda's earphones.
Mr. Fujitani tuned them.
I did the tuning, too.
I did the tuning.
There was one song I wanted you to listen to with these earphones.
That song is called Higher Higher.
I see.
The bass is strong, and you can hear the singer's voice as well.
It's a very well-balanced earphone.
I see. So the tuning is quite good, even from the store owner's point of view?
Yes, because it was chosen as No. 1.
It's the kind of tuning that everyone likes.
It's the tuning that everyone likes.
Don't use it!
I don't use it.
Then, if you say it in real life, it's even worse.
It's even worse.
Bye.
This cream soda is still on sale.
Yes, we got it and we're using it.
They match.
It's so cute.
We hope you'll use it.
Please do!
This is the wireless headphones section.
I almost didn't get a chance to introduce you earlier.
I couldn't do it.
There was something I wanted to introduce.
Yes, yes... may I ask you again?
Once again, this one.
Yes.
Vansal's
Vansal's Measure 4.
It's as pretty as it looks.
Yes, it is.
I've been wearing it around town a lot lately.
It can be used by both women and men.
It's so cute.
Does it last for 80 hours?
Eighty hours.
Really?
How many days?
More than three days.
Not more than 4 days.
So this is a hot seller right now?
They're a big seller.
It looks good, sounds good.
And the design...
It's so cute!
There are many other types.
I mean, if you're looking for something unusual, this JBL...
It's a very rare color.
It's so cute!
I thought, "I want these!
Please check out our wired headphone corner.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Do you have any last words?
I don't know if I have any more.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You don't have to make full use of it.
I hope you enjoy the next video.
Don't finish it.
Cha-cha-cha-cha!
I'm going to introduce you to the earphone corner.
Please do.
I explained it to you earlier.
I haven't said you can stop yet.
So...
I'm sorry.
Here's our most affordable wireless yam.
It's so inexpensive, isn't it?
If it's this cheap...
If you lose it or something, you can buy a new one.
It's hard for one person to shop without earphones.
That's for sure.
When I forget something today, I stop by here.
They have a great selection of earphones for about this price.
And they're waterproof and all that.
They're full of features.
It's nice.
Lun-chan is gone!
I want a Gomeranian!
Thank you very much.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
A lot.
I'm glad you've come to know
I'm glad to see that you're familiar with all kinds of earphones and headphones.
Since the last time I saw you.
I've seen a lot more.
There are a lot more headphones and earphones
I don't think there are many headphones or earphones
I don't think there are many places where you can try everything.
I don't think there's a lot of places
You can try them on and listen to them.
If you have any questions, please feel free to contact
If you have any questions, please feel free to contact Mr. Kathy.
like you just did.
I can give you a better and more thorough tour.
I don't want to talk to you by voice.
I see. I knew it.
I'd like to be able to communicate with you.
I'd like to communicate.
I want to communicate.
You've never done that before, right? I mean, not like that.
Really, what? Like that.
I'm not mad.
He's a good guy.
Nice guy.
Next time I come back, I'll show you around.
Thank you
Please come to the good Mr. Anpanman!
I have one that doesn't want to come
I won't run out.
What did you think of what we did today?
You both came up with some pretty crazy recordings.
I was really intimidated.
Let me put it this way in English.
Pinkle!
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm sorry, I won't let you watch until the end.
That's what I mean, really.
If you could say it in English, you'd have a heart attack.
What's that?
Hama-chan.
Thank you very much.
Today's experience was a lot of fun!
What do you think, Mr. Tanaka?
It's Cassy.
It's like I'm Oshima.
Enjoy!
Thank you for your hard work.
That's enough.
What?
Bye-bye.
Thank you, Mr. Kashi.
Thank you very much.
I'm tired.
I'm sorry.